Nicholas Coiner —

955 Cranbrook Ct• Davis, CA 95616• (650) 680-6022 • npcoiner@ucdavis.edu

SUMMARY

Motivated UC Davis computer science student with experience in customer service and a strong desire to learn. Proficient in Python, C++, and C# with coursework in discrete mathematics, physics, and probability & statistical modeling. Enrolled in a full stack development course at UC Davis to further develop front end and back end skills.

EDUCATION

De Anza CollegeSept. 2017 - June 2022University of California DavisSept. 2022 - Present

DEGREE/CERTIFICATION

Computer Science Degree - Associate in Science Transfer

June 2022

De Anza College GPA: 3.50

IGETC CSU June 2022

De Anza College GPA: 3.84

EXPERIENCE

Panera Bread June 2017- Sept. 2017

Cashier/Barista

Learned basic work skills, including customer service, time management, and multitasking

Whole Foods June 2018-Sept. 2018

Team Member

- Provided excellent customer service and helped to ensure smooth store operations
- Learned time management, problem-solving, and teamwork skills

Chipotle June 2018-Sept. 2018

Team Member

- Prepared food for customers and helped to keep the restaurant running smoothly
- Learned multitasking, attention to detail, and communication skills

UC Davis Coding Bootcamp

March 2023- Present

Student

Enrolled in a full stack development course provided through UC Davis to touch up on front end and back end skills in software development.

RELAVENT COURSEWORK

- Discrete Mathematics
- Physics: Mechanics, Electricity, Magnetism
- Calculus up to Differential Equations
- All Lower Division Computer Science Coursework
- ECS 132 Probability & Statistical Modeling
- ECS 152A Computer Networking

SKILLS

- Proficient in Python, C++, and C#
- Familiar with Unity Engine
- Strong communication, leadership, and teamwork skills
- Adaptable and eager to learn

INTERESTS

- Machine learning and AI systems
- Cryptography
- Predicting emergent phenomena from complex systems
- Evolutionary design of neural networks
- Large-scale data analysis and modeling